<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unit 01: Data Science on Making with Code</title>
    <link>https://cproctor.github.io/making-with-code/courses/cs9/unit01/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unit 01: Data Science on Making with Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cproctor.github.io/making-with-code/courses/cs9/unit01/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching notes (Hong Kong, 2019-2020)</title>
      <link>https://cproctor.github.io/making-with-code/courses/cs9/unit01/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cproctor.github.io/making-with-code/courses/cs9/unit01/notes/</guid>
      <description>All G9 students should be familiar with bar/scatter graphs and coordinate planes.  All students will understand linear equations Students study domain/range and functions rigorously in G10, not G9.   Statistics: all students should be familiar with mean/mode/etc. Only some students will touch on standard deviation in math class, but all students should be able to grasp the formula. Probability: students have limited/informal understanding of probability 15 class meetings  Unit Calendar Lesson 00: Our digital lives, functional program, I/O</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit 01: Teaching</title>
      <link>https://cproctor.github.io/making-with-code/courses/cs9/unit01/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cproctor.github.io/making-with-code/courses/cs9/unit01/teaching/</guid>
      <description>In Unit 1 we will build on the drawing we did in Unit 0, but we will shift our attention from imperative programming to functional programming, and shift our task domain from creative drawing to data science. This will give us an opportunity to practice writing functions, to thoroughly address variables, data types, and how functions can be composed together to solve bigger problems. Furthermore, this unit will ask students to create a different kind of product for their audience: discovery of new facts through data analysis, justification of claims, and consideration of how such arguments can be framed in ways that will feel interesting and important.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>